<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<site>
	<news>
		<post title="New Money - Thought Psycle" date="March 2, 2016">
			A wasted and worn out / musty, old house couch. Jaw slacked, back slouched / and the occasional drool drip dropping out. Screen blaring crude images all about / the money drained out of cash accounts. About the how and when / we meet the end / be the change and begin again. Proven scare tactics / that control the masses / and denying facts that / fill the air with static. So dramatic. Yet, also tragic / that most of us expect the havoc / lack the passion and act sarcastic / while burning mountains / of plastic ashes. Blind and lacking logic / cue another sheep-skinned / sleep-masked, hope deposit. A hidden stash inside your bedroom closet / as if when numbers fall it still has relevance. But, oh so benevolent / Work hard and stay well with it / Who cares, it's only debt? Got the rest of your life to make a dent... Time well spent.
		</post>
		<post title="Forced Notes - Thought Psycle" date="March 1, 2016">
			We are the back-page scribes / combating space to save a place for word tribes / that carry truth and good vibes / in hopes of prying open blind eyes. Lead hammer hits hard / hitting hopeful points of interests. Echoes dance through the halls / as it starts to take shape. Old camera pics / far-fetching hopes to stop resistance. Driving hands through the walls / of their covered up mistakes. Failed faces fall flat / fast in dark places. Light lifts lasting lulls / off of cold cases. Turning cold shoulders / towards any warm embraces / only leads to forced notes and time well wasted.
		</post> 
		<post title="Lazy Dreamer - Thought Psycle" date="February 26, 2016">
			Lost wishes pinned / flip and fall down / as the coin drops into the well. Dreams cursed and dormant / and lacking endorsements / get pulled back in by the swell. And as the hands that round clockwise / and on occasion swat flies / sit idle and wait for their turn / potential's left weighted / rather than being created / and a life's lived with no return.
		</post>
	</news>

	<collection>
		<project name="" type="" mobile="">
			<res>
				Resources
			</res>
			<desc>
				Description
			</desc>
		</project>
	</collection>
</site>